media24by7.in 2016-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Media24by7

**Privacy Policy**  
This privacy policy describes how Media24by7 uses and cares for any information that user give Media24by7 when he/she uses this website.

Media24by7 is devoted to ensure the user that your privacy is protected. Media24by7 will ask users to provide information by which they will definitely be recognized when using this website. Media24by7 occasionally tries to make changes to these policies by updating this webpage. Users can check this page frequently to confirm and ensure that they are comfortable with these changes (if any). This policy is applied and made effective from Oct 2014.  
What we collect

The information that Media24by7 may collect is as follows:

• Name of the user  
• Contact information of the user(including User’s email address and telephone no)  
• Demographic information of the users such as (Preferences and interests)

**What we do with this information**

Media24by7 collects this information to understand user requirements and provide them with improved services, and also for the following reasons:

• Media24by7 may use this information to improve our quality of products and services.  
• It may also use the user information for internal record keeping.  
• The Media24by7’s team may also use user’s information to contact them for suggestions, MARKET research and feedback purposes. We may contact the user by Email, phone, post. Media24by7 has all the rights to use the information to customize the website to provide the users with the best services according to their interests.  
• Media24by7 may occasionally send notification emails about special offers, new updates or any other information which we think user may find interesting.

**Security**

Media24by7 is committed to ensure that user’s information is safe with it. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, Our team members have put in place suitable electronic and physical managerial procedures to secure and protect the information we collect.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small sized file which will ask for permission to be stored on hard drive of user’s computer. Once the user allows cookies, the file will be added. The cookie helps lets the user know when he or she should visit a particular site or analyze web traffic. Cookies allow web apps to help user in a great personalized manner.  
The described web application can store numerous cookies as required to moderate its operations to user’s requirements. The information that can be stored is as follows:

• Login ‘remember me’ Cookie will enable you to remain signed in until they sign-out manually. Once the user sign-outs then the particular cookie will be removed, or if the website user has not logged in to the site for more than one year.  
• Basket Information (if user has not signed in), removed after successful login or a period of one year, whichever is earlier.  
• Adult Censoring will be set if the user verifies that they are 18 or over and they also agree that he/she wishes to browse Media24by7 without any censorship.  
• Information from tracking referral sites so Media24by7 can better identify where traffic is coming from.  
• Third party Cookies from the services such as Google Analytics service, to track the traffic through the Media24by7 Site in aid of enhance the quality of its service. Users may also check Google’s privacy policy for more details.

Overall, cookies help Media24by7 to provide the user with a better experience website, by allowing the website to monitor which pages user find interesting and which he/she does not. A cookie does not give Media24by7 an access to any of user information or access to their computer, other than the data users wish to choose to share with the website team.

User can surely choose to decline or accept cookies. These days, most internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but users can manually change these settings according to their preference. Changes made in browser settings may prevent the users from taking complete advantage of theMedia24by7 website.

**Links to other websites**

Media24by7 website may contain links to other websites, depending upon its interest. However, once the user leave the site by using these links, users should note that Media24by7’s team does not control the material offered on the other website. Therefore, the website and team will not be accountable for the safety and privacy of any information which the user provides on such websites and those websites are not governed by this statement of privacy. The users should check read and caution full privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Control of your personal information**

User may choose to restrict the use or collection of their personal information in following ways:  
• Whenever on the website, users are required to fill in a form, they should look for the box that they can click to choose that they do not want the information to be accessed or used for direct MARKETING purposes  
• If anytime the users have have agreed to Media24by7 for using their information for direct MARKETING purposes, Users can make changes to modify their preference by visiting their account on Media24by7 website or they can also send a request to us.  
Meida24by7 will not distribute, sell or lease the user’s personal information to third parties unless our team is required by law or we have user permission to do so. If the users allow, Media24by7 may use the users personal information to send them third party promotional information in which they may be interested.  
Users may also request details of personal information which Media24by7 holds. A small amount of fee may be payable for this information. Contact us if users would like to obtain a copy of the information held on them.

If the users believe that any of the information we hold on them is incomplete or not true, please send an email or write Media24by7 as soon as possible, Media24by7 team will verify and correct any information found to be incorrect. Further contact details are available on [CONTACT US](http://www.media24by7.com/contact-us/) page.
